"Would you like
to sing karaoke with us."
(Bernadette:)How is that a drunk text?
(Amy:)He used a period
instead of a question mark.
(Amy:)He's so wasted.
♪ Your movie's showing,
so you're going ♪
♪ Could care less about the five
you're blowing ♪
♪ Theater gets dark
just to start the show ♪
♪ You spot a fine woman
sitting ♪
♪ In your row, she's
dressed in yellow ♪
♪ She says, "Hello" ♪
♪ "Come sit next to me,
you fine fellow" ♪
♪ You run over there
without a second to lose ♪
♪ And what comes next, hey ♪
♪ Bust a move ♪
♪ You want it ♪
♪ You got it,
oh, you want it ♪
♪ Baby, you got it ♪
♪ Just bust a move ♪
♪ You want it ♪
♪ You got it, oh ♪
♪ You want it,
baby, you got it ♪
♪ Just bust a move ♪
♪ You want it, you got it ♪
♪ Oh, you
want it ♪
Hey, guys. Congratulations!
(Raj:)Thank you.
(Amy:)Hi. How are you doing?
Oh, wonderful.
(Sheldon:)I'm being musically
encouraged to bust a move.